

BAGAS PRATAMA

Jalan Veteran raya, 003/05, Kec.Kalideres, 11820 Address:

Email: bgsprtm56@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/bgsprtm56 linkedin:

https://badaso404.github.io/bgsporto.github.io/ Website:

ABOUT

Hello let me introduce my self, my name is Bagas Pratama. Im fresh graduated as associate digree and would like to have the opportunity to work as a front end and mobile developer. i already have about one years of experience in these two sections, and one years in game developer. My personality is easy to adapt to anyone, hardworking, and responsible. more details can be seen below, greetings from me to the readers.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SmartEdu-P5 Android/IOS App, Program Kreativitas Mahasiswa

Jul 2023 - Dec 2023

- · As UI/UX creator for SmartEdu-P5 application
- As Front-End Mobile Developer
- Able to communicate well with teammates
- Able to work more for the common interest

Game Developer VR, PT Pindad

Sep 2022 - Mei 2023

- Create 3D model designs for project needs.
- Program with bluprint
- Able to run Unreal Engine 5.1 fluently

Sistem Antrian pada Polres Pati, PT CMS Maju Sejahtera

Jan 2022 - Jun 2022

- As a UI/UX maker for the queuing system
- As Front-End Developer on the queuing system project
- As Project Manager in the continuity of making projects until completion

EDUCATION

Bachelor, Universitas Bina Nusantara (Binus)

Berlangsung

Information System

- Doing more in-depth learning related to the IT field
- Better prepare yourself for the world of work that is even greater in scope

Diploma, Universitas Sebelas Maret (UNS)

2020-2024

Informatics Engineering, IPK: 3.49

· Learning from the basics of IT to be ready to enter the world of work, especially the IT department.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- · Technical Skills: Design, Coding, Editing, Fotografer
- · Languages: Indonesian, English
- Certifications: BNSP Sertifikat Profesi, PKM Sertifikat Iolos pendanaan, PT.Pindad Sertifikat
- Awards/Activities: Activity participanted exhibition smart it fest teknik informatika SV UNS, Participanted and quarter final business plan compition in udayana university